Terrell Payne

terrell.r.payne@gmail.com | Euclid, OH 44143 | 216-402-7319

<u>LinkedIn</u>: <u>GitHub</u>: <u>Portfolio</u>

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer with managerial experience and over 5 years of working in customer service. Excellent problem solving skills and a creative mind to make complex but still easy to use applications for users. Constantly challenging my self to learn new things and to improve my skills. Acknowledged as employee of the month from my previous employer for helping to increase company productivity.

Technical Skills

Computer and command line proficient. Coding proficiency in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, and jQuery. Experience using Firebase, MS SQL, Node.Js, RESTful APIs. Deployment and overall management of GIT, Gitlab, Github, and Heroku.

Experience

United States Postal Service, Cleveland, OH - Supervisor/Mail Carrier

June 2014 - May 2018

- Performing daily and weekly scheduling for multiple areas operation also while maintaining accurate records of the volume of mail and determining the most effective way to process the mail to prepare for distribution.
- Preparing United States Postal Reports using multiple Microsoft applications, resolving questions and/or concerns customers may have directly or via phone, and assisting customers with shipping and receiving items.
- Acknowledged and received an award for one hundred percent scanning of parcels, helping to increase the
 overall stations percentages.
- Delivery of mail and packages to residents of customers, using an electronic scanner to log the data about deliveries and pick ups while displaying superb customer service skills interacting with postal customers directly.

Utility Partners Of America, Cleveland, OH – *Field Ser*vice Rep./Customer Service Rep. *March 2013 - May 2014*

- Safely and efficiently upgrading utility meters in customers residents following standard operating procedures and company policies, while logging the customer's information into a handheld electronic device.
- Communicating effectively with customers explaining the reasons for the utility meter upgrade an answering any questions or concerns they may have.
- Top five in meter installs over an extended time period and receiving acknowledgment of my accomplishment.
- Answering inbound calls from customers, scheduling and rescheduling appointments and assisting in resolving
 issues or any inquiries the customer may have.

Terrell Payne

terrell.r.payne@gmail.com | Euclid, OH 44143 | 216-402-7319

<u>LinkedIn</u>: <u>GitHub</u>: <u>Portfolio</u>

Education

Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, OH - Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp

• Received certificate from Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp by Case Western Reserve University.

Cleveland State University, Cleveland, OH — Business Management

Jan. 2011 - Dec. 2011

University Of Toledo, Toledo, OH – Business Management

Sept. 2009 - May 2010

Cleveland Heights High School, Cleveland Heights, OH — **Diploma**

· Graduate of 2009 class